





https://glarunsingh.github.io

About Me

RPA Specialist with 10+ years exposure to IT industry with 5+ years of expertise in RPA, experience in both product and service industry. Developed detailed project timelines and proposed new solutions that lead to significant growth in annual revenue. Built solid relationships with 10+ clients to ensure quality customer service and lean product development. Seeking a senior technical position to grow along with the firm.

Skills

- Project Management
- Creativity
- Strong Problem Solving
- Flexibility
- Leadership
- Report Metrics
- Communication Skills

Expertise

- RPA UiPath, Power Automate
- Documentations
- RE-Framework
- Document Understanding
- Insights
- Reusable/Custom Libraries
- Chatbots
- Macros
- SQL Queries

Achievements

March 2023 | Cognizant

Best Employee of the Year '22 For Effectively handled the client and won projects worth 2M.

June 2018 | Born Group

Star Performer 01 '18

best performance on effective project deliverables.

Dec 2016 | Amazon

Bugzilla Champ '16

On finding most number of bugs.

Work Experience

Arun

Singh G

Senior Software Developer

Senior Associate | Cognizant | Sep 2019 - Present

- Developed strong cross-functional relationships with big clients and stakeholders across different levels of the business.
- Owning a client's project end-to-end from requirement gathering to deployment, including CI/CD, Devops, and Github.
- Leading monthly meetings with four project teams to identify and resolve software development challenges.
- Designed custom RE-Frameworks for project needs and individually completed 25+ Bot developments, developed Insight dashboards for reporting and metrics.
- Expertise in Excel, SharePoint, SAP, Web and Citrix automation. Extensive knowledge in Macros, Queues, C#, LINQ and regex.
- Interviewed more than 100+ candidates in hiring process.

Senior Software Engineer | Born Group | Sep 2016 - Aug 2019

- Extensive experience in gathering requirements, creating Process Understanding Documents (PDDs), and providing effective solutions using Solution Design Documents (SDDs).
- Maintaining a proactive approach to customers' requests, solving huddles while automating, and clearing roadblocks to get the desired result.

Device Associate | Amazon | Jan 2014 - Sep 2016

- · Worked across 6 Generations of Amazon Kindle devices from the scratch to successful customer release and various OTA builds for 9 generation
- Took Complete ownership of Build acceptance testing (BAT/BVT) in 18 locales with respective marketplaces and decided the QA acceptance/reject based on issues faced.

Certificates

List of RPA tool certificates

UiPath - Advance RPA Developer AA - Advanced RPA profession V11 Aiwozo - Developer Certification OpenBots- Developer Certification

Fullstack certificate

Wiley - Certified Intelligent Process Automation Full Stack <u>Program</u>

Agile Testing Alliance

Certified Practitioner Manual Agile Testing

Projects

Team Lead | Incyte

- Collaborate with client to generate ideas for automation and Execute Proof of concept(s) to demonstrate automation feasibility to convert ideas to RPA project.
- Collaborate with Client Business & IT Teams as a RPA Consultant. Advocate on sprint calls, stand-ups and other meetings with stakeholders on day to day works.
- Produce estimates for projects and change requests. Assigning tasks to team and guiding them to complete the task on time.
- Develop Detailed Solution Design document, review the developed code by the team and suggest changes if required.

Project GTO CC Compliance Dashboard | Incyte

Objective of this process to get input from all the KPI participants using a standard input template and convert them to pictorial form based on formula and show the slide to GTO CC Compliance meeting.

- Acting as a Business Analyst, getting all the requirements from the client from initial conversation till the process walkthroughs
- Designed high-level and Individual process workflows, documented Product design document, giving document walkthroughs, fixing necessary changes to the document and getting PDD sign-off.
- Creating Solution design document on how to approach the process automation with detailed and elaborated design specifications.
- GTO CC Dashboard process have 4 parts which needs to be run on individual separate dates, for which developed all the 4 process in single RE-Framework and scheduled the process in orchestrator asset inputs

Project R2R Project | Thermofisher

Automation process to create Journal Entries for 1000+ processes across multiple variants involves Excel, Web app, JD Edwards, Oracle using UiPath.

- UiPath's RE-Framework has been redesigned in order to accommodate multiple processes into loaders, performers, uploaders, and reports.
- Automated 12 individual Journal entry processes involves Excel, Web browsers and Oracle applications.
- Gathering requirements, documenting and solving onboard queries during the project with respective SME's.
- Triggered successful UAT and smoke test on production environment to reduce the risks.
- Maintain the codes in GitHub, track every successful bug fix and commit the changes, with comments so other developers can understand it.

Education

2010 - 2013 | Anna University Master of Computer Application

2007 - 2010 | VIT University

Bachelor of computer application

Reference

Sathish Kumar

Consultant, qBotica

Phone: +91 97898-68062

Email: sathish.uk86@gmail.com

Prakash B

Manager, Born Group

Phone: +91 98844-75635

Email: prakash.subramanian@borngroup.com

Declaration

I hereby declare that all the information furnished above is correct to the best of my belief. I am responsible for the authenticity of all the information.

G. D. Sy